Daniel Castillo

347-259-3572 | castillodaniel1@yahoo.com

SUMMARY & SKILLS

Web Developer with 5 years of experience in Information Technology looking to leverage programming skills to collaborate working in the direction of any project.

Tech: JavaScript, CSS, HTML

Operating Systems: Linux, Macintosh, Windows 10/11/Server

Languages: Spanish (Fluent)

EDUCATION

EASTERN GATEWAY COMMUNITY COLLEGE A.T.S., Information Technology

EXPERIENCE

THE KNOWLEDGE HOUSE, Bronx, NY Innovation Fellowship - Web Developer

Sep 2023 – Present

- Build JavaScript, HTML, CSS, UX/UI design skills by participating in a project-based, software
 engineering curriculum with 100+ hours of technical instruction, and professional
 development.
- Contribute to MVP deployment for capstone projects by executing user research and agile methodology principles in addressing market opportunities with creative technical solutions using project management, communication and presentation tools like Trello, Jira, Slack and Google Suite.

PC TECHNICIAN, New York City

Jun 2018 - Present

Freelance

- Demonstrated expertise in diagnosing, troubleshooting, resolving hardware and software issues for a diverse number of clients, ensuring optimal performance, and functionality of their Operating Systems.
- Provided on-site and remote technical support to individuals and small businesses,
 delivering prompt and effective solutions to enhance productivity and minimize downtime.
- Developed strong client relationships through clear communication, reliability, and a commitment to exceeding customer expectations.

COURIER, Bronx, NY **Amazon Logistics**

Dec 2019 - Apr 2022

- Established exceptional attention to detail in sorting and organizing packages for efficient and error-free deliveries, contributing to a high level of customer satisfaction.
- Maintained a high level of professionalism and customer service, resolving delivery issues promptly and fostering positive relationships with customers.